<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on thefajarmalik</title><link>https://thefajarmalik.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on thefajarmalik</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.133.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:57:04 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thefajarmalik.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 Years of Cybersecurity Study Has Instilled an Adversarial Mindset in Me</title><link>https://thefajarmalik.com/posts/adversarial-mindset/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:57:04 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://thefajarmalik.com/posts/adversarial-mindset/</guid><description>Having almost finished my study in cybersecurity in the SECCLO master&amp;rsquo;s program, I often find myself thinking how to compromise / attack a system, be it a digital or just a physical system.
For example, a few months ago, I was trying out watches in a jewellery store in Helsinki on a cold winter day.</description></item><item><title>My journey to getting Erasmus Mundus scholarship for SECCLO</title><link>https://thefajarmalik.com/posts/journey-to-secclo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 16:00:31 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://thefajarmalik.com/posts/journey-to-secclo/</guid><description>A lot of people asked me about this, so in this post I am sharing with you my experience in getting an Erasmus Mundus scholarship for the SECCLO program.
I graduated my bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Hmm that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much it on this section. I graduated :)
I applied to Australia Awards Scholarship A few months later, I tried applying for a scholarship.</description></item><item><title>Things to consider when writing motivation letter for scholarships</title><link>https://thefajarmalik.com/posts/scholarship-motivation-letter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:00:31 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://thefajarmalik.com/posts/scholarship-motivation-letter/</guid><description>There is no right or wrong in writing a motivation letter. In this post, I merely show you how I wrote mine which got me a scholarship.
First things first: Who am I &amp;amp; why should you trust me? I was granted an Erasmus Mundus scholarship to pursue a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in SECCLO, co-funded by the Erasmus+ Programme of the European Union.</description></item></channel></rss>